<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LinearLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    style="@style/v_all_match_parent_no"
    tools:context=".ui.home.activity.NoticeDetailsActivity">

    <include layout="@layout/include_centertitletoolbar" />

    <ScrollView
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent"
        android:layout_margin="@dimen/d_10dp"
        android:background="@drawable/evaluate_bg"
        android:scrollbars="none">


        <LinearLayout
            android:paddingBottom="@dimen/d_20dp"
            android:layout_margin="@dimen/d_10dp"
            style="@style/v_all_match_parent_no">


            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/title_tv"
                style="@style/text"
                android:layout_marginBottom="@dimen/d_5dp"
                android:drawablePadding="@dimen/d_5dp"
                android:text="美肤美白管理" />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/time_tv"
                style="@style/text12color666"
                android:layout_marginBottom="@dimen/d_5dp"
                android:text="@string/time" />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/content_tv"
                style="@style/text14color666"
                android:text="皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子皮肤美白因子" />


        </LinearLayout>

    </ScrollView>

</LinearLayout>
